<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>University of Colorado Molecular Biology Program</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on University of Colorado Molecular Biology Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:33:35 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Students</title>
      <link>/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:33:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/students/</guid>
      <description>Rachel Ancar Rachel Ancar B.A., Biology, B.S. History, Univ. of Colorado Denver, 2014 Mentor: Hesselberth, Jay R. RNA cleavage and processing in nucleic acid immunity Tessa Arends Tessa Arends B.S., Cellular and Molecular Biology, Metropolitan State Univ., 2014 Mentor: Hagman, James R. The role of alternative splicing in B cells Margaret Balas Margaret Balas B.S., Biology, Metropolitan State college, 2011 Mentor: Johnson, Aaron M. Long noncoding RNAs and how they function in heterochromatin establishment and maintenance Danielle Bilodeau Danielle Bilodeau B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty</title>
      <link>/faculty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 13:33:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faculty/</guid>
      <description>Research Faculty The research interests of the more than forty program faculty include structure and function of nucleic acids, mechanisms of DNA replication, RNA transcription and mRNA translation, the structure and function of viruses, genes and gene products controlling cell cycle progression, cell death and development, protein trafficking, signal transduction, hormone receptors, and structural biology. To study these important and exciting fields, our faculty employ experimental systems such as bacteria, viruses, yeast cells, Xenopus oocytes, Drosophila, C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Program</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The Molecular Biology Program is dedicated to providing rigorous training to its students in a supportive environment. Molecular Biology faculty are members of many different departments and are applying the techniques of molecular biology to answer questions in diverse areas. Molecular biology, the science of how living things work at the molecular level, has spearheaded the recent revolution in our understanding of human disease and led to the birth of the biotechnology industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admission to the Molecular Biology Program</title>
      <link>/post/admissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/admissions/</guid>
      <description>Application deadline for admission in Fall 2019 is December 1 2018.
A completed application consists of:
 Completed application form 3 letters of reference Official transcripts GRE scores (optional for the Molecular Biology program) TOEFL or IELTS scores, if native language is not English  The average undergraduate GPA of accepted students is 3.40. Students seeking admission should have taken Organic Chemistry (2 semesters; including 1 semester of laboratory), Biology, General Physics, and college level mathematics through Calculus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic HTML Elements</title>
      <link>/post/basic-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/basic-elements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>