<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on University of Colorado Molecular Biology Program</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on University of Colorado Molecular Biology Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Admission to the Molecular Biology Program</title>
      <link>/post/admissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/admissions/</guid>
      <description>Application deadline for admission in Fall 2019 is December 1 2018.
A completed application consists of:
 Completed application form 3 letters of reference Official transcripts GRE scores (optional for the Molecular Biology program) TOEFL or IELTS scores, if native language is not English  The average undergraduate GPA of accepted students is 3.40. Students seeking admission should have taken Organic Chemistry (2 semesters; including 1 semester of laboratory), Biology, General Physics, and college level mathematics through Calculus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic HTML Elements</title>
      <link>/post/basic-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/basic-elements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>